tradusbooks.in 2014-06-30

# Online Shopping in India for Mobiles, Cameras, Watches, Clothes, Gift Vouchers – Tradus.com

At tradus.com, we believe strongly in protecting the privacy of your personal information, and in using it only in ways that have been notified to you. This Privacy Policy is a legal document which principally sets out what personal information we collect and retain, how we use it, whom we may disclose it to, the security measures we take to protect that information, and how you can correct inaccuracies in the personal information we hold. You should read it in conjunction with the tradus.com Terms and Conditions.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact tradus.com's customer service

**The full policy is displayed below :**

ibibo respects your privacy and recognizes the need to protect the personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified, such as name, address, and telephone number) you share with us. We would like to assure you that we follow appropriate standards when it comes to protecting your privacy on our web sites.

In general, you can visit the Website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. [We track the Internet address of the domains from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but the individual user remains anonymous.]

Some of our web pages use "cookies" so that we can better serve you with customized information when you return to our site. Cookies are identifiers which a web site can send to your browser to keep on your computer to facilitate your next visit to our site. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the option to decide whether or not to accept it. The information we collect and analyze is used to improve our service to you.

There are times when we may collect personal information from you such as name, physical address or telephone number. It is our intent to inform you before we do that and to tell you what we intend to do with the information. Generally, you will have the option not to provide the information, and in the future you will be able to "opt out" of certain uses of the information. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit the Website, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers and services.

ibibo will not sell, trade or disclose to third parties any information derived from the registration for, or use of, any online service (including names and addresses) without the consent of the user or customer (except as required by subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process or in the case of imminent physical harm to the user or others). ibibo will allow suppliers to access the information for purposes of confirming your registration and providing you with benefits you are entitled to.

ibibo will take appropriate steps to protect the information you share with us. We have implemented technology and security features and strict policy guidelines to safeguard the privacy of your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access and improper use or disclosure. ibibo will continue to enhance its security procedures as new technology becomes available.

By accessing this site the user agrees to let ibibo and the assistants hired by ibibo store, process and use the personal data entered by the user to justify and administrate the business and User relationship, as well as to perform and execute deals and contracts initiated through the website. This particularly concerns the User's name, address, telephone number, email address, sex and date of birth.

Any Personal Information which we collect and which we may use in an aggregated format is our property. We may use it in the aggregated format, in our sole discretion and without any compensation to you, for any legitimate purpose and you hereby confirm that you have no objection to the aforesaid use of your Personal Information.

**Notice of Grievance:**

In the event you have any grievance relating to the processing of information provided by you, you may contact our Grievance Officer at the following address:

Pawandeep Mehta Head- Customer Relations Ibibo Web Pvt. Ltd., 4th Floor, Pearl Towers, Plot No 51, Sector 32, Gurgaon, Haryana-122002 Email: [grievance@tradus.com](mailto:grievance@tradus.com)

**For any queries/ issues related to the product, please visit our help section attradus.com/help**

We request you to please provide the following information in your complaint :-

  * Identification of the information provided by you
  * Clear statement as to whether the information is personal information or sensitive personal information
  * Your address, telephone number or e-mail address
  * A statement that you have a good-faith belief that the information has been processed incorrectly or disclosed without authorization, as the case may be.
  * A statement, under penalty of perjury, that the information in the notice is accurate, and that the information being complained about belongs to you.

**This document is an electronic record in terms of Information Technology Act, 2000 and the amended provisions pertaining to electronic records in various statutes as amended by the Information Technology Act, 2000. This electronic record is generated by a computer system and does not require any physical or digital signatures.**
